Guide to the K. Leroy Irvis Papers, 1946-1995 AIS.1971.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Publications, 1946-1992; XVIII.
  - Publications and Brochures, 1960-1970; 1.
    This subseries contains two folders of brochures from the Bicentennial Commission and the Black Artist's Show.
    - Publications (1971 Original Deposit), 1946-1971 (Box 20, Folder 316)
    - Call for Achievement Program - Bicentennial Commission (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Black Artist's Show, Negro History Week, 1960-1970 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Pennsylvania History (1995 Addition), 1987-1992; 2.
    This subseries contains articles, correspondence, booklets, pamphlets, and other publication regarding Pennsylvania history. This series is arranged by subject.
    - The Pennsylvania General Assembly Bicentennial, September 18, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 269)
    - Gettysburg Reenactment, September 19, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 270)
    - Gettysburg Memorial Day Celebration - 125th Anniversary, May 25, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 271)
    - Gettysburg Celebration - Correspondence (Box 81, Folder 272)
    - Gettysburg - Various Articles (Box 81, Folder 273)
    - Gettysburg-Programs, Video (KLI's speech), Photographs (Box 81, Folder 274)
    - Gettysburg Times, May 26, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 275)
    - PA Historical - Various Booklets (Box 81, Folder 276-277)
    - Historical Pennsylvania - Various Pamphlets (Box 81, Folder 278)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 81, Folder 279)
    - Lincoln at the Wills Home and the Gettysburg Address (Box 81, Folder 280)